saveology.com 2011-12-13

# Saveology - Privacy Policy

_Please note that from time to time we may review and modify our Privacy Policy. As your visits to the Site will be subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of your visit, please review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you are aware of any modifications._

This policy is effective as of and was last updated on May 13, 2011. 

## 1\. General

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) is designed to inform you about the type of information that SaveologyDEALS, LLC (“Company”, “we,” “our” or “us”) may gather about or collect from you in connection with your use of www.Saveology.com (the “Site”). It also is intended to explain the conditions under which we use and disclose that information, and your rights in relation to that informationi. 

## 2\. Children

This Site is not intended for persons under eighteen (18) years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from persons under eighteen. 

## 3\. Gathering, Use and Disclosure of Non-Personally-Identifying Information

We collect both Non-Personally-Identifying Information and Personally-Identifying Information from you. **“Non–Personally–Identifying Information”** is information that, without the aid of additional information, cannot be directly associated with a specific person or entity. **“Personally–Identifying Information,”** by contrast, is information such as a name or email address that, without more, can be directly associated with a specific person or entity. 

Gathering Non-Personally-IdenGathering Non-Personally-Identifying Information 

### (i) Web Browsers

Like most site operators, we gather from you Non-Personally-Identifying Information of the sort that web browsers, depending on their settings, may make available. That information includes your Internet Protocol **(“IP”)** address, operating system and browser type, and the locations of the web pages that you view right before arriving at, while navigating and immediately after leaving this Site. 

### (ii) Web Cookies

A **“Web Cookie”** is a string of information that a site stores on your computer, and that your browser provides to this Site each time you submit a query to this site. We use Web Cookies to track the pages that you visit during each Site session, both to help us improve your experiences with this Site and to help us understand how this Site is being used. 

IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO HAVE WEB COOKIES PLACED ON YOUR COMPUTER, YOU SHOULD SET YOUR BROWSER TO REFUSE WEB COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THIS SITE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN FEATURES OF THIS SITE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF WEB COOKIES. IF YOU REFUSE WEB COOKIES, YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY. 

### (iii) Google Interest Based Advertising Program

In order to enhance your experience when you visit our website, we participate in the Google Interest-based Advertising Program (the “Program”) to insure that the advertisements on this Site correspond to your interests. We do this by working with Google and other Program participants who, like us, place ads on our Site and those of other Program Participants. We then share the information we collect using cookies placed in your browser in order to provide you with targeted advertising when you visit our websites. You may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google Advertising Opt Out Page: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

### (iv) Web Beacons

A **“Web Beacon”** is an object that is embedded in a web page. It is usually invisible to you but allows site operators to check whether you have viewed a particular web page or email communication. We may occasionally place Web Beacons on pages of this Site. 

You may not decline Web Beacons. However, they may be rendered ineffective by declining all cookies or modifying your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. 

#### B. Use of Non-Personally-Identifying Information

We analyze Non–Personally–Identifying Information gathered from you to help us better understand how this Site is being used. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, we are able to better design this Site to improve your experiences, both in terms of content and ease of use. We link information gathered using Web Cookies and Web Beacons to Personally-Identifying Information. 

#### C. Disclosure of Non-Personally-Identifying Information

From time to time, we may also release the Non–Personally–Identifying Information gathered from you in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of this Site. 

## 4\. Collection, Use and Disclosure of Personally–Identifying Information

As defined above, Personally-Identifying Information is information that can be directly associated with a specific person or entity. We will only collect Personally-Identifying Information that you knowingly submit to us. We will not disclose Personally-Identifying Information to third parties, except under the limited circumstances described below. 

#### A. Registration and Other Information Provided to Us

When you subscribe to Daily Deals, you may be asked to disclose Personally–Identifying Information. You may also choose to submit Personally-Identifying Information to us when you send us an email. You acknowledge and agree that we may use and store information about you in accordance with our Privacy Policy. We may also process and store your Personal Information on a server located outside of your jurisdiction. By providing your Personal Information to us, you consent to the transfer of your information across national boundaries. If you do not consent to such transfer as well as the processing and storage of your Personal Information outside your jurisdiction, you should not provide Personal Information to us. 

We use your Personally-Identifying Information to perform transactions, deliver services or information you have requested, and offer you products and services offered by our participating Merchants and Restaurants, that we believe may be of interest to you. We also use your information to contact you when necessary for customer service purposes. We may send you direct mailings about various products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply “opt-out” by the means provided for in the mailings or by contactin [privacy@deals.saveology.com](mailto:privacy@deals.saveology.com) . 

In order to manage your account(s) effectively, including servicing and processing your transactions or to let you know about products and services offered by us and our merchants and affiliated companies, we may disclose personal information to our affiliated companies. Offers for products and services from our affiliated companies are developed under conditions designed to safeguard your personal information. Our affiliated companies may send you direct mailings about their various products and services or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply “opt-out” by the means provided for in the mailings or by contactin [privacy@deals.saveology.com](mailto:privacy@deals.saveology.com) . 

When you subscribe to Daily Deals, **We collect your:**

  * Name
  * E-mail Address
  * Zip Code

In order to process your order when you purchase a Daily Deal, **We collect your:**

  * Credit Card
  * Billing Address
  * Phone Number

We use 128-bit SSL encryption to securely and automatically accept, process and manage online payments as well as to collect and store the Personal Information you provide to us. When you order products or services or provide us with information, you will be transferred to a secure server where this information is stored and managed. All of the Personal Information you provide is encrypted before it is sent to us. 

#### B. Surveys

From time to time, we may also ask you to participate in surveys designed to help us improve this Site. Any Personally-Identifying Information provided to us in connection with a survey will be used only in relation to that survey, and will be disclosed to third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy only in non-personally-identifying, aggregated form. 

#### C. Other Disclosures

Notwithstanding any other provision in this Privacy Policy, we will disclose Personally-Identifying Information in the following limited circumstances: 

##### (i) Employees; Third Party Processors; and Participating Merchants

We will disclose Personally–Identifying Information to our employees, contractors, affiliates, vendors and suppliers who process Personally–Identifying Information on our behalf or participate with us in the provision or operation of this Site. When you purchase a Daily Deal, we will provide the sponsoring Merchant with your name and Voucher Number in order for you to redeem the Daily Deal Voucher. 

##### (ii) By Law, to Protect Rights and to Comply with Our Policies

We disclose Personally–Identifying Information if: (1) required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena or court order; (2) we believe in our sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect against fraud, to protect our property or other rights, or the rights of other users, third parties or the public at large; or (3) we believe that you have abused the Site by using it to attack other systems or to gain unauthorized access to any other system, to engage in spamming or otherwise to violate applicable laws. 

##### (iii) Business Transfers; Bankruptcy

We reserve the right to transfer all Personally-Identifying Information in our possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other transfer of all or a portion of our assets. Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personally–Identifying Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if you are given notice of that transfer. Personally-Identifying Information submitted or collected after a transfer will be subject to the privacy policy adopted by the successor organization. 

##### (iv) Marketing

We may contact you by email about products and services that we think may be of interest to you. If you wish to opt out of receiving marketing emails from us, please follow the instructions at the bottom of each email. 

#### D. Security

We take reasonable precautions to protect the security of your information. However, neither people nor security systems are foolproof. Therefore, while we use reasonable efforts to protect your Personally-Identifying Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

#### E. Contests, Giveaways and other Promotions

From time to time, we may offer Site users the opportunity to participate in contests, giveaways and other promotions. Any information submitted in connection with promotions will be subject to the terms of the promotion, not this Privacy Policy. You will be given the option to consent to the use of your Personally-Identifying Information at the time you sign up for the promotion. However, your participation in the promotion will not be conditioned on the consent to use your Personally-Identifying Information for purposes unrelated to the promotion. 

## 5\. Collection and Use of Information by Third Parties Not Covered By This Agreement

Third parties are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy with respect to Personally-Identifying Information and Non-Personally-Identifying Information that you provide directly to those third parties or that those third parties collect for themselves. We do not control third-party sites that may be accessible through this Site. Thus, this Privacy Policy does not apply to information provided to third party sites or gathered by the third parties that operate them. Before visiting a third party site, whether by means of a link on this Site or otherwise, you should review its privacy policies and terms of use. 

## 6\. “Invite A Friend”

When you provide us with a friend’s name and email address either to invite them to subscribe to Daily Deals or in order to purchase a Deal for a friend, we will use their name and email address so that we may send them an email to invite them to subscribe to Daily Deals and/or to send them the Deal Voucher, and to track the success of our Referral Program. 

## 7\. To Inspect, Change or Modify Your Personal Information

Upon request, SaveologyDEALS, LLC will provide you with a readable copy of your personal information that we have on file, although we may require proof of your identity before doing so. To make such a request, contact us at support@deals.saveology.com. If you would like to modify the information that you have provided to us, you may do so via the “My Account” page.  or in writing to support@deals.saveology.com. 

## 8\. For Additional Information.

SaveologyDEALS, LLC maintains this Site from its headquarters in Ft. Lauderdale, Florida. If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy or believe that our Privacy Policy has not been complied with as to your Personal Information, please contact us as at privacy@deals.saveology.com or by United States Mail at SaveologyDEALS, LLC, 3303 W Commercial Blvd, Suite 201, Fort Lauderdale, FL 33309 or call 1-877-503-8132. 

If you no longer wish to receive daily deals from Saveology, you may [Unsubscribe Here](http://profile.saveology.com/sa_unsubscribe.jsp) .
